Wandersee, Winifred Collection of Frances Perkins Audio-Visual Materials 5982 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Winifred Wandersee Collection of Frances Perkins Audio-Visual Materials
1985-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wandersee, Winifred
5982 AV
1.56 cubic feet
1.6 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
Audio tapes of interviews with Maurice Neufeld, Mary Jean Collins, Karen DeCrow, Lois Galgay Reckitt, Alice Cook and Sonia Johnson.
8298080
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 02, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 24, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5017: Frances Perkins Correspondence and Memorabilia 5065m: Frances Perkins Letter to Donald Stetson 5812: Interviews about Frances Perkins 5982: Winifred Wanderse Research Notes on Frances Perkins and Incomplete Manuscript 6002 AV: James S. Perkins Collection of Movie Film Studies of Shop Operations 6027: James Secor Perkins Additional Papers /3012: Alice Cook Papers /3007: Maurice Neufeld Papers /4039: Milton R. Konvitz Papers /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4073: James O. Morris Office Files /4107: Kheel Center Additional Cataloging Project Work notes /4297: ILR School Biography Files 5001 mf: American Association for Labor Legislation Records on Microfilm 5001 mf: American Association for Labor Legislation Records on Microfilm 5002: American Association for Social Security Records 5143: Anna Weinstock Schneider Papers 5221: Max Meyer Papers 5225: ALES Records 5226: National Council On Household Employment Records 5235: National Consumers League Records 5277: Workers Education Bureau of America Records 5549: Edwin S. Smith Papers 5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5 5584: National Archives and Records Service Copies of Federal Documentation on Black Workers 5616: Isaac Max Rubinow Papers 5676: International Fur and Leather Workers Union Records 5709 mf: National Women's Trade Union League of America Records on Microfilm 5724 mf: Cigar Makers International Union Records on Microfilm 5780 AV: ILGWU Audio-Visual (AV) 5780 P: ILGWU Photographs 5780 P N45: ILGWU 4x5 Negatives of Photographs 5780/002: ILGWU David Dubinsky Correspondence 5780/177: ILGWU Communications Department Biography Files
Collins, Mary Jean; Cook, Alice; DeCrow, Karen; Johnson, Sonia; Neufeld, Maurice F.; Perkins, Frances; Reckitt, Lois Galgay; Wandersee, Winifred D.
8298080
- Maurice Neufeld #1 (Box 1)
  - Maurice Neufeld #1 (Box 1)
- Maurice Neufeld #2 (Box 2)
  - Maurice Neufeld #2 (Box 2)
- Mary Jean Collins, NOW, Wash. D.C. 10/15/85 (Box 3)
  - Mary Jean Collins, NOW, Wash. D.C. 10/15/85, 1985 (Box 3)
- Karen DeCrow Interview 8/8/85 (Box 4)
  - Karen DeCrow Interview 8/8/85, 1985 (Box 4)
- Unlabeled (Box 5)
- Get right with God (Box 6)
  - Get right with God (Box 6)
- Unlabeled (Box 7)
- Unlabeled (Box 8)
- Kolb Interview, Pt. 1-2 (Box 9)
  - Kolb Interview, Pt. 1-2 (Box 9)
- Lois Galgay Reckitt - 6/25/85 (Box 10)
  - Lois Galgay Reckitt - 6/25/85, 1985 (Box 10)
- Alice Cook interview/Perkins - Nov. 15, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Alice Cook interview/Perkins - Nov. 15, 1990 (Box 11)
- Williams on Perkins (Box 12)
  - Williams on Perkins (Box 12)
- Sonia Johnson -- 10/16/85 (Box 13)
  - Sonia Johnson: 10/16/85, 1985 (Box 13)
- #29 - 4/6/86 Master, 1986 (Box 14)